Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 13: Carroll Gardens, circa 1990 - circa 2011
  - Casa Rosa, 384 Court Street between Carroll Street and President Street, circa 1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Exterior Mormon visitor center, Long Island College Hospital Continuum, 340 Court Street, between Sackett Street and Union Street, circa 1995 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 142 Luquer Street, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, Sparky's Ale House, 481 Court Street at Nelson Street, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, Helen's Place, 396 Court Street, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse (Roy Cohn), 405 Clinton Street (between President Street and Union Street), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, The Red Rail, Henry Street at Sackett Street, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Carroll Gardens Park [Carroll Park] between Court Street and Smith Street and President Street and Carroll Street, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Brooklyn Apartment, 192 President Street between Clinton Street and Henry Street, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - EXT Car Lot, 508 Smith Street at Centre Street, circa 2005 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - EXT Car Lot, Smith Street and 9th Street, circa 2005 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - 218 Degraw Street (between Henry Street and Clinton Street), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    This location was scouted for Sex and the City.
  - EXT/INT School, P.S. 32, Hoyt Street (between Union Street and President Street), 2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Court Street (Carroll Gardens), 2010 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. The photographs depict Court Street between 2nd Place and 3rd Place, Court Street between Carroll Street and 1st Place, Carroll Street between Court Street and Smith Street, 3rd Place between Court Street and Smith Street, Court Street between 1st Place and 2nd Place.
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Clinton Street (Carroll Gardens), 2010 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. The photographs depict Union Street between Clinton Street and Court Street, Clinton Street between Sackett Street and Union Street, Clinton Street between Union Street and President Street.
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 102 2nd Street (between Hoyt Street and Bond Street), Carroll Gardens, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - I/E Abby Black, 1 2nd Place at Henry Street, Carroll Gardens, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - EXT Subway Station, Carroll Street Station, Carroll Gardens, circa 2010 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse - Abby, 308 Clinton Street between Baltic Avenue and Kane Street, Carroll Gardens, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 405 Clinton Street (between Union Street and President Street), 2011 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - INT/EXT Machine Shop, 521 Carroll Street, between 3rd Avenue and 4th Avenue, Carroll Gardens, Neptune Machine, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 199 Nelson Street at Dennett Place, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Black World, Dennett Place at Luquer Street, Carroll Gardens, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - INT/EXT Misc. Black House - 603 Henry Street, Carroll Gardens, circa 2011 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Series 14: Clinton Hill, 1991 - 2011
  Series 14: Clinton Hill includes photographs of apartments, houses, churches, public housing, and a funeral parlor.
  - INT/EXT Funeral parlor, Piro Funeral Home, 251 Dekalb Avenue at Vanderbilt Avenue, Clinton Hill, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    This folder was categorized under "Funeral Parlors."
  - Sweatshop: Hall Industrial Complex, 21 Hall Street at Flushing Avenue, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Clinton Hill, Clinton Avenue (between Park Avenue and Myrtle Avenue), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 159 Willoughby Avenue at Hall Street, Apt. 2C, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    This location was scouted for Return to Paradise.
  - 132 Willoughby Avenue [Clinton Hill], 1999 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    This folder was categorized under "Apartments/lofts."
  - 87 Cambridge Place (between Fulton Street and Gates Avenue), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 339 Washington Avenue between Dekalb Avenue and Washington Avenue, 1999 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Loft apartment, 16 Waverly Avenue between Park Avenue and Flushing Avenue, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - EXT Brownstone, 180 Clinton Avenue (near Myrtle Avenue), Clinton Hill, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - INT/EXT 289 Washington Avenue (between Willoughby Avenue and Dekalb Avenue), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 284 Clinton Avenue, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - INT/EXT Warehouse, 156 Flushing Avenue at Vanderbilt Avenue, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - EXT Townhouse, 278 Clinton Avenue, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - EXT Townhouse, 321 Clinton Avenue, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Underwood Park, Edmonds Playground, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - INT Apartment/Loft, 320 Washington Street Apt. 2C [Clinton Hill], 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Housing Projects, Lafayette Gardens, Lafayette Avenue and Franklin Avenue, Clinton Hill, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Military morgue, Hall Street Cold Storage, Hall Street (between Flushing Avenue and Park Avenue), circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Repop Furniture, 68 Washington Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    This location was considered for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close.
  - INT EXT Loft, 42 Washington Avenue (just off Flushing Avenue), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Courtyard and Church/Rectory, St. Mary's Episcopal, 230 Classon Avenue and Willoughby Avenue, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - EXT Church, Emmanuel Baptist Church, 34 St. James Place and 279 Lafayette Avenue, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - EXT St. Mary's Episcopal Church, 230 Classon Avenue at Willoughby Avenue, Clinton Hill, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - St. Joseph's College, 245 Clinton Avenue (between Willoughby Avenue and Dekalb Avenue), circa 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Estate sale, 287 Dekalb Avenue at Waverly Avenue, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Houses."
  - INT/EXT Estate sale, 289 Dekalb Avenue at Waverly Avenue, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT Black residence, 365 Washington Avenue, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 357 Washington Avenue, Clinton Hill, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Black Residence, 284 Clinton Avenue, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Clinton Hill Co-ops, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Chocolate factory lofts, 275 Park Avenue, circa 2010 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    This location was scouted for Extremely Loud and Incredibly Close. This folder was categorized under "ELIC BRKLYN 'hoods, townhouses, houses, APTs / Lofts."
  - 69 Vanderbilt Avenue [Clinton Hill], circa 2010 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Chocolate factory lofts, 275 Park Avenue [Clinton Hill], circa 2010 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - INT/EXT Black - Various, 4/6 Downing Street at Gates Avenue, Clinton Hill, Bedford-Stuyvesant [Broken Angel House], 2011 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse - Abby Black, 320 Clinton Avenue, Clinton Hill, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone - Various Blacks, 32 St. James Place at Lafayette Avenue, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 275 Clinton Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Apt. 2-1, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 275 Clinton Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Apt. 3-4, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - INT Loft, Black various, 275 Park Avenue at Washington Avenue, Apt. 6B, 2011 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Series 15: Cobble Hill, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 15: Cobble Hill includes photographs of apartments, houses, hospitals, funeral parlors, bars, restaurants, and stores.
  - Empty Bar, 115 Columbia Street at Kane street, circa 1990 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Hospital, Long Island College Hospital, 358 Henry Street, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Funeral Parlor, Cobble Hill Chapels, 171 Court Street, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - EXT/INT Brownstone, 130 Pacific Street, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Movie Theater, Cobble Hill Cinema, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Bar, The Long Island Bar, 110 Atlantic Avenue (at Henry Street), Cobble Hill, circa 1995 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Rooftop view, Long Island College Hospital garage, Atlantic Avenue at Hicks Street, Cobble Hill, circa 1995 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - INT Bar, Cousins, 160 Court Street, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - INT Bar, Long Island Restaurant and Bar, 110 Atlantic Avenue, corner of Henry Street and Atlantic Avenue, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Cobble Hill Aquarium, pet store, 268 Court Street, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    This location was scouted for One Fine Day.
  - Inaka Restaurant, 158 Court Street, 1996 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - INT Bar, Peter's Waterfront Ale House, 136 Atlantic Avenue (between Clinton Street and Henry Street), 1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 13 Douglass Street, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Apartment, 33 Warren Street, Apt. 1, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - EXT/INT Apartment, 39 Douglass Street, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - INT Italian Restaurant: Sam's Restaurant, 238 Court Street, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - INT Chemo Hospital Room, Long Island College Hospital, Radiation Oncology department, 339 Hicks Street (between Amity Street and Atlantic Avenue), 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Example of Cobble Hill apartment, 22 Verandah Place, circa 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 280 President Street (between Court Street and Smith Street), circa 2000 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse Apartment, 238 President Street (between Court Street and Clinton Street), Cobble Hill, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Roy Cohn Townhouse, 19 Strong Place (between Kane Street and Degraw Street), Cobble Hill, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 24 Butler Street, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - INT/EXT Cohn townhouse, 26 Strong Place (between Kane Street and Degraw Street), Cobble Hill, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - EXT/INT Bar / Restaurant, Cousins II, 160 Court Street, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - EXT Prior's, 122 Amity Street (between Clinton Street and Henry Street), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - EXT Brownstone, 278 Clinton Street at corner of Warren Street, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - EXT Townhouse, 321 Clinton Street (between Kane Street and Degraw Street), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - EXT Brownstone, 274 Clinton Street (between Warren Street and Verandah Place), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 16 Butler Street (between Smith Street and Court Street), 2002 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Cobble Hill Park, Clinton Street and Congress Street, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 155 Congress Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - INT/EXT Carriage House, 32 Verandah Place, Cobble Hill (between Henry Street and Clinton Street), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - EXT Brownstone / Max's, 179 Congress Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - EXT Grandma's (NY for Boston), 22 Tompkins Place between Degraw Street and Kane Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - EXT Grandma's (NY for Boston), 45 Strong Place between Degraw Street and Kane Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - EXT Grandma's (NY for Boston), 15 Tompkins Place between Degraw Street and Kane Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - EXT Grandma's (NY for Boston), 13 Tompkins Place between Degraw Street and Kane Street, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - INT Kitchen, 30 Strong Place, Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - EXT Grandma's House, 45 Strong Place between Kane Street and Degraw Street, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - INT/EXT Italian restaurant/café, Café on Clinton, 268 Clinton Street (between Warren Street and Verandah Place), Cobble Hill, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: 179 Court Street, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: 179 Court Street, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - EXT Grandma's house, Clinton Street at Congress Street, Cobble Hill Park, circa 2005 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Residence, 28 Tiffany Place, 4th Floor, circa 2005 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    This location was scouted for Mr. Wonderful. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Apartments."
  - 206 Warren Street, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - INT Restaurant, Bucco Lupo, 391 Henry Street, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - INT Brownstone, 170 Pacific Street, Cobble Hill, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - INT Townhouse, 51 Strong Place, Cobble Hill, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - INT Townhouse, 226 Warren Street, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - INT Townhouse, 177 Baltic Street, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - INT Townhouse, 229 Baltic Street, circa 2010 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - INT/EXT Misc. Black, 36 Strong Place (between Kane Street and Degraw Street), 2010 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - INT/EXT Black, 16 Verandah Place, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 149 Baltic Street, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - I/E Black Residence, 26 Verandah Place, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 169 Congress Street (between Clinton Street and Henry Street), 2011 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 367 Henry Street (between Amity Street and Bergen Street), 2011 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 356 Clinton Street (between Kane Street and Degraw Street), Cobble Hill, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 367 Henry Street (between Amity Street and Bergen Street), 2011 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series 16: Coney Island, 1987-2010
  Series 16: Coney Island contains photographs of restaurants, amusement parks, the boardwalk, Maimonides Park (formerly Keyspan Park), streets, and subway around the Coney Island neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - INT Riviera Catering, Coney Island, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    This location was scouted for She-Devil and Goodfellas.
  - Gargiulo's Restaurant, Coney Island, Bamboo, circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Gargiulo's Restaurant, Coney Island, Bamboo, circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Riviera, Coney Island, Chateau Bleu, circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - EXT View of Skyline: From Stillwell Avenue Subway Station (Stillwell Avenue and Surf Avenue), 1992 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Coney Island, circa 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Seedy hotel/club, Dreamland Freak Museum, 3006 West 12th Street between Surf Avenue and Bowery Street, Coney Island, circa 1995 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - EXT/INT Ice cream store, Carvel's, 1220 Surf Avenue at Stillwell Avenue, Coney Island, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - EXT Amusement park, Coney Island, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    This folder includes photographs of the Thunderbolt wooden roller coaster.
  - El Dorado, Coney Island, circa 2000 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Boardwalk at West 15th Street, Boardwalk at West 10th Street, Coney Island, circa 2000 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - EXT Streets, Coney Island, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    This folder includes photographs of Surf Avenue at West 12th Street and Stillwell Avenue at Mermaid Avenue.
  - Coney Island, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    This folder includes photographs of Surf Avenue at West 10th Street, Boardwalk at West 12th Street, West 10th Street at Boardwalk, Boardwalk at West 19th Street, Boardwalk at Stillwell Avenue, Stillwell Avanue at Surf Avenue.
  - Coney Island, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    This folder contains photographs of the Cyclone roller coaster at Astroland and Nathan's Famous.
  - Coney Island beach and boardwalk at West 10th Street, Astroland, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - EXT Charlie's Amusement, Coney Island, 1021 Bowery Street (between West 12th Street and Stillwell Avenue), 2004 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Keyspan Park, 1904 Surf Avenue (between West 19th Street and West 20th Street), Coney Island, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Coney Island, West 10th Street at Surf Avenue, Frank's, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Date, New York Aquarium, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Astroland Amusement Park, The Cyclone, 1000 Surf Avenue at West 10th Street, Coney Island, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Nathan's on the Boardwalk, The Grill House, Boardwalk at West 12th Street, Coney Island, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - South Street alternative: Stillwell Avenue, Surf Avenue, Mermaid Avenue, Neptune Avenue, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Coney Island: Surf Avenue at West 12th Street, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Stadium Tunnels, Keyspan Park [1904 Surf Avenue], 2009 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - INT/EXT Restaurant, Peggy O'Neill's, 1904 Surf Avenue, Coney Island, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - EXT Coney Island Beach, West 10th Street at Boardwalk, Coney Island, circa 2010 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - EXT Black World, Pier [Pat Auletta Steeplechase Pier], Coney Island, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - EXT Black World - Coney Island various, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - EXT Black World, Boardwalk, Coney Island, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - I/E Black World - subway, West 8th Street Q, B MTA, Coney Island, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Series 17: Crown Heights, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 17: Crown Heights includes photographs of apartments, clubs, bars, churches, parks, the Interfaith Medical Center, Bedford Atlantic Armory, and the streets and subway around the Crown Heights neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Classon Avenue and Bergen Street, Crown Heights, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dean Street and Grand Avenue, Crown Heights, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Dean Street and Underhill Avenue, Crown Heights, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Dean Street Station (at Franklin Avenue), Crown Heights, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "S" Line Subway Stops, Dean Street, Franklin Avenue Shuttle, circa 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Interfaith Hospital [Interfaith Medical Center], circa 1990 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, lot at 643 and 647-649 Washington Avenue between St. Marks Avenue and Bergen Street, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - EXT Subway, Shuttle train in Brooklyn, Dean Street, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Classon Avenue, south of Atlantic Avenue, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - EXT Park, Brower Park (Park Place and Brooklyn Avenue), 1995 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 742 Montgomery Street at Albany Avenue, Apt. 9D, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment: 1265 Pacific Street between Bedford Avenue and Nostrand Avenue, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Armory Drill Floor, 1579 Bedford Avenue (at President Street) [Bedford Atlantic Armory], circa 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Brower Park, Brooklyn Avenue and Kingston Avenue, Prospect Place and Park Place, Crown Heights, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Arthur S. Somers Park, Eastern Parkway at Rochester Avenue, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - INT Soul Brothers, Gray's Sports Club, 720 Prospect Place at Rogers Avenue, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    This location was scouted for American Gangster. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Bars and Diners."
  - INT Soul Brothers, Imperial Bikers, 652 Franklin Avenue at St. Marks Avenue, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - INT Soul Brothers, Monoco Lounge, 154 Utica Avenue between Prospect Place and St. Marks Avenue, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - INT Soul Brothers, The Hut, 828 St. Johns Place at Nostrand Avenue, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - EXT/INT Bar, Starlite Lounge, 1084 Bergen Street at Nostrand Avenue, Crown Heights, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - EXT Church/School/Rectory, St. Bartholomew's Episcopal Church, 1227 Pacific Street at Bedford Avenue, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - EXT Church, Bedford Central Presbyterian Church, 1200 Dean Street and Nostrand Avenue, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - EXT Church, Bedford Central Presbyterian Church, 1200 Dean Street and Nostrand Avenue, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - EXT Church, Union United Methodist Church, New York Avenue (between Bergen Street and Dean Street), 2007 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Hebron Seventh-day Adventist Bilingual School, 920 Park Place at New York Avenue, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Church of St. Mark, 1417 Union Street, St. Mark's Day School, 1346 President Street at Brooklyn Avenue, circa 2007 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Brower Park, Brooklyn Avenue at Park Place, circa 2010 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Crown Heights, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    This folder includes photographs of President Street, Ebbets Field Apartments, Bedford Avenue at Sullivan Place.
- Series 18: Cypress Hills, 1997-2007
  Series 18: Cypress Hill includes photographs of streets, subway, a church, and a school in the Cypress Hills neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - EXT Neighborhood: Crescent Street and Fulton Street, Cypress Hills, 1997 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - EXT Driving Shot / El Train, Jamaica Avenue between Logan Street and Dexter Court, Cypress Hills, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - INT / EXT School, P.S. 65, The Little Red Schoolhouse, Richmond Street (between Ridgewood Avenue and Fulton Street), Cypress Hills, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - EXT Church, Presbyterian Church of the Redeemer, 435 Etna Street at Eldert Lane, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    This location was scouted for Doubt and reconsidered for Salt.
- Series 19: Downtown Brooklyn, 1992-2010
  Series 19: Downtown Brooklyn includes photographs of restaurants, bars, and city government buildings in the Downtown Brooklyn neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Brooklyn municipal building, 211 Joralemon Street, Downtown Brooklyn, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Civil Court, 120 Schermerhorn Street, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Board of Education building, 110 Livingston Street, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Former Cinart Theater, Court Street between Schermerhorn Street and State Street, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Junior's Restaurant, 386 Flatbush Avenue (at Dekalb Avenue), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - INT Bar, Kevin Barry's, 56 Willoughby Street, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - INT Bar, O'Keefe's Bar and Restaurant, 62 Court Street, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Supreme Court (EXT), Adams Street, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Diner, Donut House, 387 Jay Street, circa 2000 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Office - Municipal, Kings County Supreme Court building, 360 Adams Street, circa 2000 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - INT Courtroom, Brooklyn Borough Hall, Joralemon Street and Court Street, circa 2000 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Nurse Association of Brooklyn, Inc., 111 Livingston Street, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - EXT Street, Sands Street at Jay Street, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - EXT Brooklyn street, bank, court, Brooklyn courthouse - Supreme Court, Court Street (between Remsen Street and Montague Street), 2000 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - INT Brooklyn Borough Hall, 2nd Floor Office, Chris' Office, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: Civil Law Practice, 125 Livingston Street, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: 161 Livingston Street, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Metro Star Cafe [369 Jay Street], Downtown Brooklyn, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Trent's office, Long Island University, Brooklyn Campus - chancellor's office, circa 2005 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - INT Langley, Kings County Supreme Court, circa 2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - EXT/INT City Hall, Brooklyn Borough Hall, 209 Joralemon Street at Court Street, circa 2005 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - INT Brooklyn Borough Hall / 2nd floor rotunda and office, circa 2005 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Brooklyn Borough Hall, 209 Joralemon Street at Cadman Plaza West and Court Street, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - [Brooklyn Borough Hall, 209 Joralemon Street at Cadman Plaza West and Court Street], 2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - EXT Streets, Park Avenue and Navy Street, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Kings County Supreme Court, 360 Adams Street, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - INT Auction Room, Brooklyn Borough Hall, 209 Joralemon Street at Court Street, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)